export default data10 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Is St Helena part of the UK?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "No"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Where is Theatreland?",
        options: ["Docklands", "London’s east end", "London’s west end", "London’s south end"],
        correct_option: "London’s west end"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "What other name is given to Diwali?",
        options: ["The Festival of Lights", "Ash Wednesday", "Good Friday", "Easter Monday"],
        correct_option: "The Festival of Lights"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Which of the following charities helps the environment?",
        options: ["NSPCC", "Shelter", "Friends of the Earth", "Crisis"],
        correct_option: "Friends of the Earth"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "Which of the following was a crucial aerial battle fought between Germany and Britain during WWII?",
        options: ["The Battle of Britain", "The Battle of Worcester", "The Battle of Dunbar", "The Battle of Marston Moor"],
        correct_option: "The Battle of Britain"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "By law, radio and television coverage of the political parties must be balanced and so equal time has to be given to rival viewpoints.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Where did the Spanish Armada come from?",
        options: ["France", "Spain", "Italy", "South America"],
        correct_option: "Spain"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "What is the name of the War Memorial located in Whitehall?",
        options: ["Dumfries", "Cenotaph", "Royal Crescent", "The White Tower"],
        correct_option: "Cenotaph"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "The UK government has never suspended the Northern Ireland Assembly.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "Who is responsible for the opening of the new parliamentary session each year?",
        options: ["The Prime Minister", "The Speaker", "The Queen", "The Home Secretary"],
        correct_option: "The Queen"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "What flower did William Wordsworth write about?",
        options: ["Rose", "Daffodil", "Thistle", "Shamrock"],
        correct_option: "Daffodil"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "When was the Domesday Book written?",
        options: ["After the Viking invasion", "After the Norman conquest", "After the last Roman invasion", "After the Anglo-Saxon invasion"],
        correct_option: "After the Norman conquest"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "When is St Andrew’s day celebrated?",
        options: ["17th April", "31st December", "1st March", "30th November"],
        correct_option: "30th November"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Can the National Anthem be played if the Queen is not present?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "Yes"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "When were the first coins in Britain made?",
        options: ["The Stone Age", "The Bronze Age", "The Iron Age", "The Middle Ages"],
        correct_option: "The Iron Age"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Who was Emmeline Pankhurst?",
        options: ["A suffragette", "A nurse", " A doctor", "A scientist"],
        correct_option: "A suffragette"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "Who did Britain fight against in the Crimean War?",
        options: ["Turkey", "Russia", "France", "Germany"],
        correct_option: "Russia"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "How old do you have to be to buy alcohol in the UK?",
        options: ["17", "18", "19", "20"],
        correct_option: "18"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Which British sportsman was captain of the English cricket team?",
        options: ["Bobby Moore", "Sir Ian Botham", "Sir Steve Redgrave", "Sir Jackie Steward"],
        correct_option: "Sir Ian Botham"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "In which Japanese cities did the United States drop atomic bombs in August 1945?",
        options: ["Osaka and Nagasaki", "Hiroshima and Osaka", "Osaka and Kyoto", "Hiroshima and Nagasaki"],
        correct_option: "Hiroshima and Nagasaki"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "By 1200, the English ruled an area of Scotland known as the Pale, around Edinburgh:",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "Which of the following countries does not take part in the Six Nations Championship?",
        options: ["Wales", "Italy", "Germany", "France"],
        correct_option: "Germany"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Who became Queen after Edward VI?",
        options: ["Elizabeth I", "Queen Mary", "Anne Boleyn", "Catherine of Aragon"],
        correct_option: "Queen Mary"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "The right to life and the right to liberty and security are some of the principles included in the European Convention of Human Rights:",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
    
]